No. No, no.
No, don't take him.
No! No!
You promised me!
You said I could keep this one!
No!
And this would be
the baby's room.
You don't like it, do you?
I don't think he does.
Shhh.
But we do.
I mean, we do, right?
Here you go.
Why are you being so stubborn?
He only likes this one pacifier.
He's very picky.
You'd think I'd be better
at this.
I used to be
a pre-school teacher.
And if I understood correctly,
you were looking for something
with a slightly timeless feel?
Is that right?
Yeah, I... I was.
- And we are.
- Yeah.
And this uh... this definitely
fits the bill.
It's very cool.
Right?
And of course,
we'd be happy to remove
any of the furniture
that's not to your liking.
But we did only leave the pieces
that are true antiques.
Oh well,
now, that's why I'm here.
Yeah.
I mean, why... why we're here.
Yeah, and you're never gonna
beat the price.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shhh, shhh, shhh, shhh.
- Here, here you go.
- Yeah.
We love a good price.
Okay.
Good.
Well, how about we take a gander
at the barn?
Sounds good to me.
Okay, right this way.
Well, you heard the woman.
Let's go take a gander.
Okay.
All right.
I almost got it here.
Got it.
Here we go.
Oh man.
Wow.
What do you think, little man?
You want to go see where
daddy's gonna work, huh?
Let's go.
Let's go take a look.
Now, we don't have
the electricity
turned on out here yet.
But everything else
works like a dream.
Look, daddy's gonna
keep his supplies over here.
Put an exam table over there.
We have all the space
in the world now.
Which means more money,
you know what I'm saying,
right, little man?
Much better than that
noisy cramped city.
It's kind of perfect, right?
The house...
It's been listed for a while.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm, it has.
But we have done
some heavy sprucing.
And uh...
Why do you think
no one's bought it?
Well...
there was an... an incident.
Yeah, we don't want to know.
We do.
What happened?
Well, it's gonna sound worse
than it was,
but there was a suicide.
Uh... double homicide.
The girl killed her baby
and then her father.
Okay, as I said, we're good.
Yeah, well, here's the report.
I suppose you're out.
No.
We'll take it.
Are you sure?
You know, I don't mind
a little haunting.
Besides, it's all in the past.
We are focused on the future,
right?
Well, let's get
your John Hancock
on some preliminary paperwork.
Here, do you see mommy?
Oh, okay, okay.
That's okay.
The commute out to the animals
from the city
was getting to be
a bit of a slog.
Mmm. Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
So I was thinking, you know,
why not come to them
and you know, Sara can do
her teaching wherever,
when she's ready to go back.
But really, I just...
I just hope that
the change of scenery helps,
because the city is
not good for us.
Not since the baby was born.
Sara, especially.
The depression and all.
We tried everything else,
so this is kind of it.
Mmm-hmm.
And I just need one more
right there.
Okay.
Phew.
Yay.
Hi.
What do you think?
Well, we're homeowners now.
Or at least we're on our way.
Is there room for three?
- I think so.
- Yeah.
Where's that...
Do you have the blue pacifier?
It's right here. Oh.
Oh, hey. You got it. You got it.
It's stuck, okay.
Here you go, little man.
Yeah. Yeah.
Very nice.
Do you remember our first night
at the apartment on Fourth?
No electricity, no plumbing.
This is better.
Well, should we take this
bad boy for a spin, huh?
Buckle your seat belt,
little man.
Wow.
Wee!
I'm proud of you.
I think it's almost bedtime,
huh?
Yeah, I'll take him.
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah. Please stay.
Enjoy the rest of the show.
Thanks, homeowner.
You're welcome, homeowner.
Hey.
Yeah, it's a good song, huh?
Wow, it's mommy and daddy.
Scary?
Just, it's j... mmm-hmm.
Ooh.
Hey.
Sorry.
This... this door won't open.
Yeah?
Let me try.
Hmm.
I told you.
We bought a house
and we didn't
even see every room.
Amateur move.
Okay, I'm gonna go
get some tools.
Woah.
This is awesome.
I thought
they just had a daughter.
There were two.
Oh.
I'm... I'm... I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to scare you.
I knocked, but no one answered.
So, you...
You just walked upstairs?
That's how we do things
around here.
But I guess you folks
aren't from around here.
How could you tell?
Are those for us?
Yup.
Thank you.
That's... that's very kind.
I can't drink it.
But my husband here
loves a good beer.
Right?
Sara Davis.
Oh.
And this is my husband, Alex...
who likes beer.
Loves it, actually.
Oh.
Hey.
So um, uh, uh, who are you?
Chris Renner.
I live next door.
Probably the closest thing
you have to a neighbor,
so I wanted to say hi
and... give you those.
Saw there's a hole
in your screen porch.
Thought you might
need help fixing.
Oh, I'm actually pretty handy
for being city slicker
that I am.
We wouldn't mind a little help.
Right?
Yeah.
Uh, I'm a vet, if you have
any animals that need tending.
Don't have animals.
And that would be our son Liam.
He loves to cry.
Hopefully, it won't make its way
over to your house.
That's all right.
Well, I can show you out.
I'm on my way downstairs.
What do you think, little man?
You like it?
You want to know something?
This gonna be...
This gonna be your happy place.
Yeah.
This is where you're going
to learn to walk and talk
and read and write,
and eventually drive.
I know.
Scary, right?
This is where
you're gonna grow up.
Big and tall.
And then one day,
you'll bring home
your very first girlfriend
or boyfriend.
- I don't mean to presume.
- And...
And eventually you're gonna
start your own family
and you're gonna
build memories for your kids
like the ones we made here.
I hate to break it
to you, though.
Those memories are gonna be
really tough to beat.
All right, I'm finished.
Are you ready
for your first night
in a brand-new crib?
You like it?
Well, I think it's time
for a little night-night song.
Hmm?
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
It was just um...
I was just... why is...
Why is the crib in here?
I thought we were gonna put it
in his bedroom?
I thought we agreed
that he was gonna
sleep in his bedroom?
Yeah.
I mean, it's his first night.
So, how about here tonight
and there tomorrow?
- I just...
- Right?
You know,
it's also our first night.
Okay, okay.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to christen
our new home.
Is that okay?
He's right there.
Yeah, I know. He's asleep.
We're not gonna corrupt
a young man.
I... I don't... just...
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Remember what the doctor said?
This is totally natural.
It's all part of the process.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
if I was giving any signals.
I just...
No, no.
No, it's okay.
Yeah.
Let's just get some sleep, huh?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay, come here.
Just come here, my angel.
Yeah? Come on.
Come on,
it's time for breakfast.
Okay.
Come here, my love.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
All right, all right.
Okay.
Okay. Here, let's try this.
Let's try this.
Come here. Okay.
Okay, here you go. Yeah.
Here you go. Yeah.
Still not taking, huh?
Not today.
Oh, you look handsome.
I'd let you take care
of my pigs.
Well, thank you.
The real estate agent
gave me a list of farms
within 50 miles.
It's might mean
some late nights.
At first, at least.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't distract him, please.
I'm sorry. I just...
I just want him to eat.
Love you.
Good bye, little man.
Are you gonna take care
of mommy today, hmm?
Keep her company.
Keep her out of trouble.
Hey, what do you want to do
about this uh, this box?
Oh, I think there's a crawlspace
behind that wardrobe
in our bedroom.
I better start pumping some iron
if I'm gonna move that thing.
It's monstrous.
All right.
I'm gonna work
on his room today.
So, we can get the crib
in there.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Oh, oh, okay.
Okay, you finished.
You finished.
Yes, you're so good.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here.
Ready?
This little monster
went to the grocery store.
Wait, why would a monster
have to go to the grocery store?
Monster's got to eat.
Hold on.
Look.
Look, look, look.
Look what I have.
Wow.
Look, mommy's music box.
Okay, okay.
Okay, my love. Come on.
Come here.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, ready?
Ready?
Come here.
Are you ready?
Okay, let's try the other side.
Yeah, let's try the other side.
Oh, it's okay.
I know. I know.
It's okay.
Come her, Liam.
Come on.
Come here, let's try this.
Okay.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay. It's okay.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's okay, it's okay.
You not hungry?
The windows in Liam's room
are nailed shut.
Yeah, it's probably
storm protection, I guess.
Then why aren't the windows
in the rest of the rooms
like that?
I... I don't know.
But I can take 'em out.
How is Liam?
Liam was fine.
I um, saw that you moved him.
Yes.
It's what we said
we were gonna do.
I got his room all ready.
How was your day?
Well, those farms
are... quite scattered.
It's gonna be a bit more work
than I had anticipated.
The last farm I saw
was over an hour away.
But all the farmers I met
were really eager.
One of them even asked me
to come back tomorrow.
That's great.
I'll get him.
You're eating.
Sara.
Oh.
Um...
you feed him and I'll feed us?
Sara?
Yes.
Good morning, my lo...
Where were you?
Uh, I'm... I'm here.
I'm... I'm good.
It's time to start the day.
- Are you...
- Yes.
- Going to...
- Yes, yes.
Can you stop by that guy's house
on your way out?
Uh, Renner?
Yeah, sure.
Um, why
I want him to fix that screen
on the porch.
I'm sorry.
I've gotta hit the road.
- You'll ask him, right?
- Yeah.
Oh, have you seen
Liam's pacifier?
It's not in his crib.
It should be.
I'll just get a new one.
Right, little man?
You got to have that
blue pacifier, hmm?
Hey, I like the bow.
It's... it's pretty.
Thanks.
It's a ribbon.
Come here.
Okay.
You okay?
I fixed the screen.
You're back.
Good.
There's something wrong
with this litter.
Well, we can test the father.
Or eliminate the litter.
I prefer the more
conservative approach myself.
But it would involve
the killing of the father.
Kill the father.
So, you knew the family
that lived here?
How?
I've lived in the same place
my whole life, give or take.
So, you knew the girl... Anna?
Mmm.
And... and the boy,
what... what was his name?
Andrew.
He wasn't in any of the reports.
What happened?
They said two murders...
Yeah, I... I...
I know about that part.
What I meant was why.
Well, something like
that never just happens.
I found the windows in her room
nailed shut.
Hmm.
Why?
So, no one outside
would find out.
Find out what?
What he was uh... up to.
So... so he... he was... he was...
I saw her.
Last night.
You look like her.
Here you go.
Yeah, here you go.
Okay.
Liam!
You're okay. You're okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's alright now, it's alright.
It's alright, sweetheart.
I thought he would be
the best thing
that ever happened to me.
He will be.
But it's not.
I mean, I look at him
and I just feel...
I feel so uncomfortable.
Just like... he's an intruder
or something.
I don't know, I just...
I just don't...
I don't feel right.
Hey.
That's just the depression,
okay?
That's not you.
It will go away.
It's just not going away.
I mean, the depression.
I'm gonna help you
get through this.
I promise.
How long has he been like that?
Did you feed him yet?
Okay, I'll get him.
Okay, here you go, little man.
Here's mommy.
Go to momma.
Got him.
Yeah, they didn't have
any pacifiers.
Got him a truck.
I'll look again today.
Okay.
I love you, man.
So, it was the mother.
Were there any other litters?
Just those.
That's lucky.
It's... it's just the two litters
and of course, the mother.
Uh, injection or bolt gun?
The bolt gun is cheaper,
but less humane.
Bolt gun.
I would prefer the injection
and I could cover
the difference in cost.
I don't need your charity.
Bolt gun.
Tomorrow.
I owe you a better answer.
You asked why.
The children's mother died
when the boy was born.
That's what made him so rotten.
So... Robert and Anna...
How could he do that to her?
His way of grieving, I suppose.
It's why she killed the baby.
What about the boy?
What happened to him?
He was ignored.
Blamed for the mother's death.
You were close to him?
Why isn't he in
any of the reports?
I've seen them both now.
Anna and Robert.
Well, I don't believe
in that kind of thing.
But if I did, here would be
just the place for it.
Did Robert have an axe?
What happened to
the Solomon boy?
Well, I'm not really supposed...
He wasn't killed.
So, what happened to him?
Well, he was handed over
to the state, of course.
He lives in the house next door.
Well, it's more of a shack,
really.
His name is Chris.
It's Renner.
It used to be Andrew.
But when he came back,
he had the new name,
a new look.
We all knew.
People see lights on
in the house.
They'd say it was haunted.
But it was just him.
He just wanted to be home.
We gave him his space.
After what he'd seen.
That is, until you came along.
What?
What do you want?
Okay, okay. Look, look, look.
Look at the truck, Liam.
Look.
Don't you love your truck?
You want your pacifier?
All right, I'm gonna find it.
I'll find your pacifier.
Okay, you want to help me?
Come on. Let's try together.
Let's find it together, yeah?
Come on. Let's find it.
Let's go.
- Ah, oh my God.
- What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry.
You scared me.
I was just looking
for the pacifier.
- Come on, let me see him.
- It's okay.
What? Okay.
Hey, little man. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, let's go.
All right, let's go, buddy.
Let's go play with your
new toy truck.
It wasn't a great day.
What happened?
There's something wrong
with a whole bunch of baby pigs.
And they need to be...
eliminated.
The mother, too.
How?
I... I don't wanna talk about it.
Alright.
What happened
to the toy truck, Sara?
The toy truck?
It's up in his room.
I just saw it.
I was playing with it
in front of his crib.
Well, it's not there.
I don't know then.
I don't know how things
just keep disappearing.
Well, I haven't moved them.
Well, neither did I.
- Maybe you forgot.
- I'm with him every day.
I would know
if I moved something.
And I didn't.
Okay, well, I didn't touch them.
So who did?
Okay.
You know, it isn't just
Liam's things
that have gone missing.
Wedding portrait seems to have
disappeared as well.
Come here.
Come here, sweetie.
Right. I got ya.
Hey, you're okay.
Here, come here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
- Liam!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You okay? You okay?
Liam.
Mm-hmm.
You threw out the milk.
What did you do to my music box?
And the photo
with my preschool class?
Why would you do that to them?
Why?
So, is that why you
threw out the milk
and you left our child
at the edge of the stairs?
Because of a music box
and a photograph?
So, you did do it?
I called a doctor.
A psychiatrist.
Dr. Klein recommended him.
He specializes in post-part um.
You called Dr. Klein?
He'll be here shortly.
And until then,
I'm gonna watch Liam.
I can't... leave him alone
with you anymore.
Alex, no.
No, no, no. Please.
Um, it's just the...
The new environment.
Exactly.
We're in... new space
and you're feeling
out of control.
But it's not...
It's not just that.
It's this house.
I just don't feel like
I'm alone here.
Okay, I can understand
why you would feel that way.
Especially, after learning about
what happened here.
I didn't rip my face
out of that photo
and I...
I didn't smash my music box.
Well, maybe you just
don't remember it.
I mean, it... it must be hard
to see yourself like that
back when things were easier.
And the childhood memories
are difficult, too.
That's the only
logical explanation, Sara.
These things don't just happen.
There's nothing wrong
with this house, okay?
What about our wedding portrait?
Very nice.
- Dr. Carver.
- Mr. Davis.
- Should I...
- Oh yeah.
He'll be fine.
Um, I'll...
I'll call if I'm running late.
Shouldn't be more than an hour.
Fine.
Now, where were we?
I see your last doctor gave you
a coping mechanism
for your anxiety,
which was brought on by...
By the baby.
Along with the depression?
Yes.
And you refused medication?
I didn't refuse medication.
I just...
You opted out so you could
continue to breastfeed.
To continue to connect
with my son.
But you stopped seeking care
once you moved.
The move was supposed
to fix things.
And has it?
No.
It's hasn't.
Would you care to elaborate
on that?
Come here.
You know what?
Let me try this a different way.
Have you been seeing things
or hearing things?
No, I haven't.
Alex has really been there
for me.
We've always been there
for each other.
Well, then why did you
place your son
at the top of the stairs
last night?
It was an accident.
Um, I... I thought that
the gate was closed.
I'd like to start you
on some medication.
That's an anti-psychotic.
I'm not...
I want to keep breastfeeding.
But your husband said
you threw out your milk.
You know, everybody told me
how euphoric this would all be.
How I was gonna feel love
I'd never felt before.
I don't feel any of that.
And I'm embarrassed.
Then I look at him
and I feel guilty,
and resentful, and sad.
I mean, I feel everything
except for the one thing
that I was supposed to feel.
And I want to feel that
so badly.
To feel like he's mine.
And I know that's never
gonna happen with a pill.
Thank you.
Thank you for saying all that
to me.
I really mean it.
You know, the emotions
that you're feeling,
they're not real.
But your psychosis is.
And it needs to be corrected.
I think you can go now.
You can go.
I'm the neighbor.
Mr. Davis called me.
They're right there.
Hmm, hmm. Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me...
that you were her brother?
Uh...
I don't think
I've ever told anyone.
I wanted to keep it to myself.
My way of grieving.
But you came back.
You kept it all up.
It's my home.
Not exactly in my price range,
so...
I wanted... I wanted to keep her
in the picture, too,
but she was...
all tied up,
standing in front of him.
Were there others?
Babies?
Yeah, yeah, eventually.
Three altogether.
What happened to the other two?
But they weren't mentioned
in the reports.
Yeah, they wouldn't have been.
Why not?
They're not...
They're here.
I'm going back.
That explains
all the toys missing,
all the sounds,
and all the scratching.
The wardrobe.
I wouldn't go poking around
in there again.
There's a reason
it is where it is.
And a reason nobody but him
can move it.
How was it?
He wants to put me
on medication.
Okay.
Well, we could put Liam
on formula.
Are... are you serious?
Well, I... I'm just saying,
if that's what we need to do.
Will you listen to me?
The only time I feel
connected to Liam
is when I'm breastfeeding.
And even that is tenuous.
But it's... it's something.
And you know that.
I've told you.
I've told Dr. Klein.
How many times
do I have to say it
before people stop trying
to take that away from me?
Jesus, Sara.
I'm trying to help you.
I have been trying.
I have tried so hard to be
whoever, whatever it is
that you need me to be,
and now I feel like
I'm losing my family.
And it is happening
right in front of me
and I can't fucking stop it!
It's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, little man.
What you think, huh?
How about a little bath, yeah?
Hmm?
Does it tickle? Does it tickle?
Can I join?
I took the medication.
Yeah.
- You want the duck, huh?
- You like the cow?
Moo.
What's that?
Hmm.
Oh, I should um, take him.
There we go, hi.
Hey, that's one of my clients.
He's got a cow in labor.
She's about to lose
her calf. Baby.
Go. Seriously.
We'll be fine.
Really, I... I took the pill,
remember?
Right?
Okay, I'll be back really soon.
Okay. Okay.
That's okay. He'll be back.
It's okay.
Oh, let's get the duck.
It's okay. It's okay.
Alex?
Alex.
Sara?
Sara.
Alex.
Liam!
Please.
No.
I know who you are.
I know what he did to you.
I'm not like that.
You are.
We've seen you.
You've hurt him.
No. No, no, I didn't.
That's not true.
It is.
I didn't mean to.
Yes, you did.
Please just give him back to me.
No.
Give him back to me.
No!
He's mine.
You're mine.
Yeah.
I got you, I got you.
Yes, my sweet boy.
Hi. You're mine.
You're mine.
He's mine.
Good morning.
I made breakfast.
It's over.
Thank you.
Hmm, who's laughing?
You like dancing?
Can I swing?
We'll be right there,
little man.
I'm not that little.
Three, two... one.
Woo!